Guide to the John H. Eyer Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- John H. Eyer papers, 1930-1986; 1950-1974; 3932-001; 18.24 cubic feet (16 boxes) plus 1 oversize folder
  - UNITED PAPERMAKERS AND PAPERWORKERS, 1958-1969; SERIES 4 (Box-folder 8/23-27, Oversize folder 1)
    - United Papermakers and Paperworkers, 1958-1964; Contains issue of United Paper, February 28, 1959 (Box-folder 8/25)
    - Teamsters and Paperworkers Unions, 1965-1969; Contains issue of Teamster Paperworker, October 1966 (Box-folder 8/26)
    - United Papermakers and Paperworkers Constitution, 1957 March 6 (Box-folder 8/27)
    - Oversized Signs, Flyers, and Publications, 1956-1970 (Folder:oversize 1)
      - Sign Advertising Special Meeting for Members of United Papermakers and Paper Workers and International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers on Contract Offer, circa 1964
  - UNIFORM LABOR AGREEMENT, 1952-1969; SERIES 5 (Box-folder 8/28-10/3)
    Contains correspondence, agreement drafts, notes, procedures, political cartoons, and photographs documenting negotiations of the Uniform Labor Agreement between the International, United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Pacific Coast Association of Pulp and Paper Manufacturers, and the Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers.
    - Uniform Labor Agreement Negotiations, 1956 (Box-folder 8/28)
    - Uniform Labor Agreement Negotiations, 1958 (Box-folder 8/29-30)
    - Uniform Labor Agreement Negotiations, 1959 (Box-folder 8/31)
    - Uniform Labor Agreement Negotiations, 1960 (Box-folder 8/32)
    - Uniform Labor Agreement Negotiations, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 8/33)
    - Uniform Labor Agreement Negotiations, 1964 (Box-folder 9/1)
    - Uniform Labor Agreement Negotiations, 1962 (Box-folder 9/2)
    - Uniform Labor Agreement: Health and Welfare, 1958-1967 (Box-folder 9/3)
    - Uniform Labor Agreement Negotiations, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 9/4)
    - Uniform Labor Agreement: Resources on Bargaining Procedures, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 9/5)
    - Uniform Labor Agreement Negotiations, 1963 (Box-folder 9/6-7)
    - Uniform Labor Agreement Negotiations with International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, United Papermakers and Paperworkers, and Pacific Coast Association of Pulp and Paper Manufacturers, 1957 (Box-folder 9/8)
    - Uniform Labor Agreement and Joint Board of Health and Welfare, 1961-1967 (Box-folder 9/9)
    - Uniform Labor Agreement and Wage Stabilization Board: Political Cartoons and Correspondence, 1952 (Box-folder 9/10)
    - Uniform Labor Agreement Bargaining, 1953 (Box-folder 9/11)
    - Uniform Labor Agreement Negotiations, 1954 (Box-folder 9/12)
    - Uniform Labor Agreement Negotiations, 1955 (Box-folder 9/13)
    - Uniform Labor Agreement Negotiations, 1964 (Box-folder 9/14)
    - Uniform Labor Agreement Negotiations: Agreement Drafts and Notes, 1964 (Box-folder 9/15-16)
    - Uniform Labor Agreement of 1964 Between Pacific Coast Association of Pulp and Paper Manufacturers and Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers (Box-folder 9/17)
    - Uniform Labor Agreement Negotiations, 1965 (Box-folder 9/18)
    - Uniform Labor Agreement Negotiations, 1966 (Box-folder 9/19)
    - Uniform Labor Agreement Negotiations, 1967 (Box-folder 9/20)
    - Uniform Labor Agreement and Pensions, 1959-1967 (Box-folder 9/21)
    - Uniform Labor Agreement, Pensions, and Unfair Labor Practices National Labor Relations Board Case, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 9/22)
    - Pacific Coast Pulp and Paper Manufacturers "Permanent Classification Committee Interpretations: Uniform Labor Agreement", 1955 (Box-folder 10/1)
    - Safety and Uniform Labor Agreement: Eyer's Article Drafts and Reference File, 1962 (Box-folder 10/2)
    - Uniform Labor Agreement Negotiations with International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, United Papermakers and Paperworkers, and Pacific Coast Association of Pulp and Paper Manufacturers: Photographs, 1957 (Box-folder 10/3)
  - PAPER WORKER ORGANIZATIONS AND COUNCILS, 1954-1972; SERIES 6 (Box-folder 10/4-28)
    Contains meeting, conference, convention, and educational program materials from the Pacific Coast Pulp and Paper Mill Employees Association; employer association, Pacific Coast Association of Pulp and Paper Manufacturers; the 4-Union Coordinating Committee; pulp and paper worker state and regional councils; the Rank and File Movement for Democratic Action and Northwest Committee for Union Justice; and related unions in the lumber and saw mill and paper printing industries.
    - Pacific Coast Pulp and Paper Mill Employees Association Conferences, 1955-1960 (Box-folder 10/4)
    - Pacific Coast Pulp and Paper Mill Employees Association Educational Program, 1954-1958 (Box-folder 10/5)
    - Pacific Coast Pulp and Paper Mill Employees Association: Correspondence, Board Meeting Minutes, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 10/6)
    - Pacific Coast Pulp and Paper Mill Employees Association: Correspondence, Board and Council Meeting Minutes, 1957 (Box-folder 10/7)
    - Pacific Coast Pulp and Paper Mill Employees Association: Conference, Education Awards, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 10/8)
    - Pacific Coast Pulp and Paper Mill Employees Association: Secretary-Treasurer Change, Education Awards, 1960 (Box-folder 10/9)
    - Pacific Coast Pulp and Paper Mill Employees Association: Union Education Ment Award Correspondence, Notes, Representative List, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 10/10)
    - Pacific Coast Pulp and Paper Mill Employees Association Research and Education Director George W. Brooks Resignation, 1962 (Box-folder 10/11)
    - Pacific Coast Pulp and Paper Mill Employees Association Conventions: Rose City Local 242's Resolutions and Bylaws, 1951-1962 (Box-folder 10/12)
    - Pacific Coast Association of Pulp and Paper Manufacturers and Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers: Multi-Company Bargaining and Two Level Strike, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 10/13)
    - Pacific Coast Association of Pulp and Paper Manufacturers and Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers: Equal Employment Opportunity Commission and Female Workers, 1968 (Box-folder 10/14)
    - Pacific Coast Association of Pulp and Paper Manufacturers: Death of Sidney W. Grimes, 1972 February 29 (Box-folder 10/15)
    - Pacific Coast Association of Pulp and Paper Manufacturers Correspondence, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 10/16)
    - Union Agenda Submitted to the Pacific Coast Association of Pulp and Paper Manufacturers, 1967 (Box-folder 10/17)
    - Pulp and Paper Worker State Council Meetings, 1955-1961 (Box-folder 10/18)
    - State Pulp and Paper Workers Councils, 1954-1967 (Box-folder 10/19)
    - Western Canada Council of Pulp and Paper Mill Unions: Conference Proceedings, Pension Plan Analysis, 1960-1962 (Box-folder 10/20)
    - 4-Union Coordinating Committee Meetings, 1955-1958 (Box-folder 10/21)
    - Oregon State American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO): Legislative Issues Conference, Committees, Summer School Program, 1959-1962 (Box-folder 10/22)
    - Northwest Council of Pulp and Paper Workers Annual Meeting Minutes, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 10/23)
    - Western Council of Lumber and Saw Mill Workers U.B.C. of J. of A. Conventions: Correspondence, Press, Flyer, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 10/24)
    - Printing Specialties and Paper Products Union and Western Conference of Specialty Unions, 1963-1972 (Box-folder 10/25)
    - Remarks of William Perrin at the Northwest Council Meeting of the International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers and the United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Lewiston, Idaho, 1963 October 4 (Box-folder 10/26)
    - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Rank and File Movement for Democratic Action, and Northwest Committee for Union Justice, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 10/27)
    - Northwest Council of Pulp and Paper Workers: Letter from Ralph E. Davison to Bill Walker, 1962 July 5 (Box-folder 10/28)
  - JOB ANALYSIS AND TRAINING, 1952-1970; SERIES 7 (Box-folder 10/29-11/15)
    Contains meeting minutes, reports, correspondence, notes, training materials, photographs, ephemera, and published material related to union member training and job analyses performed by John Eyer and other representatives of the International and AWPPW locals.
    - Job Analysis Program Directors' Minutes, Reports, and Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 10/29)
    - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Development of Training and Education Positions, 1956-1959 (Box-folder 10/30)
    - Job Analysis Summaries, 1953-1964 (Box-folder 10/31)
    - Plant Analysis Committee Monthly Reports, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 10/32)
    - Job Analysis Training Program Materials, circa 1956-1966 (Box-folder 10/33)
    - Job Analysis Training Schedule, 1956-1961 (Box-folder 10/34)
    - Job Rate Evaluation Program Miscellaneous Items for Bargaining Text, circa 1969 (Box-folder 10/35)
    - Job Analysis Program Monthly Board Reports, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 10/36-37)
    - Job Analysis Study Committee: Survey, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 10/38)
    - Job Analysis Committee: Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers President William Perrin's Correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 10/39)
    - Job Analysis Directors, 1952-1966 (Box-folder 10/40)
    - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Job Analysis Representatives, 1957-1967 (Box-folder 10/41)
    - Association of Federal, State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) Local Union Training Program, 1968 (Box-folder 10/42)
    - Paper Worker Union Training Program: Photographs and News Clippings, 1956-1961 (Box-folder 10/43)
    - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers 1959 Union Training Program, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 10/44)
    - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers 1961 Union Training Program, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 10/45)
    - Labor Education at Colleges and Universities, 1961-1967 (Box-folder 11/1)
    - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Union Training Program Correspondence and Reports, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 11/2)
    - Correspondence on International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Published Materials, 1957-1961 (Box-folder 11/3)
    - Union Training: Correspondence About John Eyer's Travel Plans, 1957 (Box-folder 11/4)
    - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers 1960 Union Training, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 11/5)
    - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Union Training Program Correspondence, 1953-1955 (Box-folder 11/6)
    - AFL-CIO and Other Education Programs, 1955-1958 (Box-folder 11/7)
    - Washington State Council of County and City Employees, Council 2, circa 1967-1968 (Box-folder 11/8)
    - Association of Federal, State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) Instructor Training, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 11/9)
    - Union Seminar at Reed College, Portland, Oregon, 1956 (Box-folder 11/10)
    - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Union Training Classes, 1958 (Box-folder 11/11)
    - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Union Training Class, Portland, Oregon, 1958 (Box-folder 11/12)
    - International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Seminar at Reed College and Mount Hood National Forest Field Trip, 1958 (Box-folder 11/13)
    - Pacific Coast Labor Law Conference Roster, Agenda, and Notes, 1968 March 29 (Box-folder 11/14)
    - John Eyer's Assorted Notes on Labor, circa 1960s (Box-folder 11/15)
  - PAPER COMPANIES, 1948-1974; SERIES 8 (Box-folder 11/16-14/21)
    Contains correspondence; news clippings; pamphlets and booklets; contract agreements, including drafts with notes; minutes; reports; legal materials, including National Labor Relations Board case records; and several photographs documenting relations between major paper companies and paper worker unions. Subject matter includes elections; collective bargaining and negotiations, including decisions of locals to withdraw from the Uniform Labor Agreement; job promotions and benefits; grievances and arbitration; strikes; and investigations into paper mill water pollution. Subseries A-I are arranged by company name. Subseries J relates specifically to pensions and K to arbitration cases.
    - Boise Cascade, 1962-1973; Subseries A (Box-folder 11/16-18)
      - Boise Cascade Corporation and Pacific Northwest Locals: Withdrawal from Uniform Labor Agreement, 1969 (Box-folder 11/16)
      - Boise Cascade Corporation Locals: Collective Bargaining, Health and Welfare Plans, 1962-1970 (Box-folder 11/17)
      - Boise Cascade Corporation: Assorted News Clippings, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 11/18)
    - Crown Simpson, 1966-1967; Subseries B (Box-folder 11/19-21)
      - Fairhaven, California, Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers and National Labor Relations Board Election for Bargaining Representative at Crown Simpson, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 11/19)
      - Fairhaven, California, Crown Simpson, Paper Workers, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers: Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers vs International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Election, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 11/20-21)
    - Crown Zellerbach, 1957-1974; Subseries C (Box-folder 11/22-27)
      - Crown Zellerbach Corporation: News Clippings, Agreements, Bargaining, 1957-1974 (Box-folder 11/22)
      - Crown Zellerbach Corporation: Health and Welfare Plans, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 11/23)
      - Port Townsend, Washington, Local 175: Elections, Officers Rosters, Arbitration and Grievances, 1963-1967 (Box-folder 11/24)
      - Port Townsend, Washington, Local 175 and Crown Zellerbach Corporation: Contract Negotiations, Agreement Proposal and Drafts, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 11/25)
      - Port Townsend, Washington, Local 175 and Crown Zellerbach Corporation: Arbitration and Grievances, Training, 1958-1970 (Box-folder 11/26)
      - Los Angeles, California, Crown Zellerbach Corporation and Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Local 266: Company Amendments to Agreement, 1967 March 14 (Box-folder 11/27)
    - ITT Rayonier, 1957-1974; Subseries D (Box-folder 11/28-12/1)
      - ITT Rayonier Incorporated: Benefits, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 11/28)
      - ITT Rayonier Incorporated: Assorted News Clippings, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 11/29)
      - ITT Rayonier Incorporated: Pollution, Uniform Labor Agreement, Negotiations, National Labor Relations Board Case, 1959-1970 (Box-folder 11/30)
      - Hoquiam, Washington, Local 169 and Rayonier Corporation: Promotion ladders, Grievances, Meeting Minutes, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 11/31)
      - Hoquiam, Washington, Local 169: Grievances and Arbitration, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 11/32)
      - Port Angeles, Washington, Local 155 and ITT Rayonier: Strike, Grievances, Job Analysis, News, 1957-1970 (Box-folder 11/33)
      - Port Angeles, Locals 155, 730, 269, and 169: Bargaining, Member and Officer Rosters, Agreement Drafts, Ground Rules, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 12/1)
    - Kimberly-Clark, 1962-1974; Subseries E (Box-folder 12/2-4)
      - Kimberly-Clark Corporation: News Clippings, Benefits, Uniform Labor Agreement, 1966-1974 (Box-folder 12/2)
      - Fullerton, California Local 672 and Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers: Contract with Kimberly-Clark, 1969 March 26 (Box-folder 12/3)
      - Fullerton, California, Local 672 and Kimberly-Clark Corporation: Collective Bargaining, Arbitration, 1962-1971 (Box-folder 12/4)
    - Scott, 1959-1972; Subseries F (Box-folder 12/5-28)
      - Scott Paper Company: News Clippings and Company Produced Materials, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 12/5)
      - Scott Paper Company Everett Plant Labor Agreement, 1967 (Box-folder 12/6)
      - Everett, Washington, Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Local 183 and Scott Paper Company: Arbitration, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 12/7)
      - Everett, Washington, Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Local 183: Monthly Manpower Summary, 1967 June 1 (Box-folder 12/8)
      - Everett, Washington, Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers Local 183: Income Statement, 1971 (Box-folder 12/9)
      - Everett, Washington, Local 183: Court Order Regarding Access to Funds, 1970 (Box-folder 12/10)
      - Everett, Washington, Scott Paper Company and Locals 183 and 644 Agreement: Eyers Notes, 1967 (Box-folder 12/11-12)
      - Everett, Washington, Scott Paper Company and Locals 183 and 644 Agreement: John Swanson's Notes, 1967 (Box-folder 12/13)
      - Everett, Washington, Locals 183, 644, 10, and 20: Assorted Records, 1956-1971 (Box-folder 12/14)
      - Everett, Washington, Scott Paper Company and Locals 183 and 644 Strike, 1967 (Box-folder 12/15)
      - Everett, Washington, Locals 272, 20, 644, and 183, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 12/16)
      - Everett, Washington, Locals 644, 20, 183: Job Ladders, Health and Welfare, Contract Agreements, Minutes, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 12/17)
      - Everett, Washington Locals: Area Rep John R. Swanson's Local 10 Contract Agenda and Quarterly Report, circa 1969 (Box-folder 12/18)
      - Everett, Washington, Locals 183 and 644: Contract Agenda Submitted to Scott Paper Company, 1971 May 28 (Box-folder 12/19)
      - Everett, Washington, Labor Agreement Between Scott Paper Company and Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers: John R. Swanson's Notes, 1967 (Box-folder 12/20)
      - Everett, Washington, Locals 183 and 644: Scott Paper Company Proposed Labor Agreement Changes, 1969 May 20 (Box-folder 12/21)
      - Everett, Washington, Local 644: Equipment Safety Assessment, circa 1969 (Box-folder 12/22)
      - Everett, Washington, Local 183 and Scott Paper Company: Arbitration, 1967 (Box-folder 12/23)
      - Everett, Washington, Locals 183 and 644: Contract Negotiations, Strike, 1967 (Box-folder 12/24)
      - Everett, Washington, Locals 644 and 183 and Scott Paper Company: Contract Drafts with Notes, 1967 (Box-folder 12/25)
      - Correspondence between John Eyer and George Brooks: Scott Paper Strike, Convention, and Painters District Council 9, 1967 (Box-folder 12/26)
      - Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers and Scott Paper Company: Collective Bargaining and Benefits, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 12/27)
      - Water Pollution Control Commission Waste Discharge Permit, 1970 March 31 (Box-folder 12/28)
    - Simpson Lee, 1962-1973; Subseries G (Box-folder 12/29-33)
      - Simpson Lee Paper Company, Everett, Washington, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 12/29)
      - Simpson Lee Paper Company, Everett, Washington: Benefits, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 12/30)
      - Everett, Washington, Simpson-Lee Paper Company and Local 272: Court Orders on Release of Funds, 1970 (Box-folder 12/31)
      - Everett, Washington, Simpson-Lee Paper Company and Local 272: Closure of Plant and National Labor Relations Board Case, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 12/32)
      - Ripon, California, Local 863 and Simpson Lee Company: Officers Roster, Job Schedule, Unified Labor Agreement Withdrawal, Bylaws, 1962-1971 (Box-folder 12/33)
    - Weyerhaeuser, 1963-1973; Subseries H (Box-folder 12/34-39)
      - Weyerhaeuser Company, Snohomish County, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 12/34)
      - Weyerhaeuser Company: News Clippings, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 12/35)
      - Weyerhaeuser Company, 1963-1970 (Box-folder 12/36)
      - Everett, Washington, Weyerhaeuser Company and Everett Kraft Mill: Local Negotiations, Case Study, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 12/37)
      - Everett, Washington, Weyerhaeuser Company and Local 10: Arbitration, 1970 (Box-folder 12/38)
      - Everett, Washington, Weyerhaeuser Sulphite Mill Closure and Employee Relocation, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 12/39)
    - Other Companies, 1952-1974; Subseries I (Box-folder 12/40-13/20)
      - Alaska Lumber and Pulp Company: Health and Welfare, 1960 (Box-folder 12/40)
      - Borden, Incirca: News Clippings, Negotiations, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 12/41)
      - Everett, Washington, E. A. Nord Company: Dental Benefits, 1972 April 6 (Box-folder 12/42)
      - Fireboard Corporation: Pensions, Contract Negotiations, Uniform Labor Agreement Withdrawal, News Clippings, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 13/1)
      - Fibreboard Corporation: Health and Welfare Plans, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 13/2)
      - Vernon, California, Locals 336 and 254 and Fibreboard Corporation: Correspondence, Officers Rosters, Arbitration, 1956-1971 (Box-folder 13/3)
      - Georgia-Pacific Corporation: Health and Welfare, Labor Agreement, Picketing, News Clippings, Photographs, 1960-1974 (Box-folder 13/4)
      - Toledo, Oregon, Local 13 and Georgia-Pacific: Agreement and Ground Rules Drafts and Notes, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 13/5)
      - Toledo, Oregon, Local 13 and Georgia-Pacific: Negotiations Offer, circa 1969 (Box-folder 13/6)
      - Grays Harbor, Washington, Local 315 and Grays Harbor Paper Company: Pension Meetings, 1967 (Box-folder 13/7)
      - Turlock, California, Local 854 and International Paper Company: Correspondence, Report of Negotiations, 1960 (Box-folder 13/8)
      - International Paper Company Assorted Records, 1957-1974 (Box-folder 13/9)
      - Union Gap / Yakima, Washington, Local 380 and Kieckhefer Container Company: International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Election Ephemera, Correspondence, National Labor Relations Board Petitions and Reports, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 13/10)
      - Longview Fibre Company, 1954-1974 (Box-folder 13/11)
      - Seattle, Washington, Longview Fibre Company Monthly Production Summary, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 13/12)
      - Ukiah, California, Local 723 and Masonite Corporation: Contract, Correspondence, 1958-1963 (Box-folder 13/13)
      - Menasha Corporation, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 13/14)
      - Flagstaff, Arizona, Ponderosa Paper Products Corporation: Election of United Papermakers and Paperworkers and Association of Western Pulp and Paperworkers Contestation, 1965 (Box-folder 13/15)
      - Publishers Paper Company, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 13/16)
      - R-W Paper Company: Benefits, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 13/17)
      - Richmond, California, Local 617 and Western Kraft: Negotiations, 1967 (Box-folder 13/18)
      - New York, New York, Local 107: "An Open Letter to All Sister Locals" About Teamster Recruitment at Standard Bag Company, 1963 November 1 (Box-folder 13/19)
      - Western Paper Converting Company Employee Board of Appeals Case, 1963 (Box-folder 13/20)
    - Pensions, 1948-1968; Subseries J (Box-folder 13/21-14/17)
      - Bemis Brothers Bag Company and Pension Negotiations, 1956-1961 (Box-folder 13/21)
      - Boise Cascade Paper Corporation Pension Negotiations, 1951-1967 (Box-folder 13/22)
      - Crown Zellerbach Corporation Pension Plans, 1959-1967 (Box-folder 13/23)
      - Fibreboard Products Corporation Pension Plans, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 13/24)
      - Georgia-Pacific Paper Company Joint Pension Trust: Proposed Pension Plan Drafts, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 13/25)
      - Georgia-Pacific Paper Company Joint Pension Trust, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 13/26-27)
      - Georgia-Pacific Paper Company Joint Pension Trust, 1962 (Box-folder 13/28)
      - Georgia-Pacific Paper Company Joint Pension Trust, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 13/29)
      - Georgia-Pacific Paper Company Joint Pension Trust, 1963 (Box-folder 13/30)
      - Georgia-Pacific Paper Company Joint Pension Trust, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 13/31)
      - Georgia-Pacific Paper Company Employee Newsletter, 1963 December (Box-folder 13/32)
      - Georgia-Pacific Puget Sound Division Pension Plan, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 13/33)
      - Ketchikan Pulp Company Pension Plan, 1957-1961 (Box-folder 13/34-36)
      - Kimberly Clark Corporation Retirement Plan and Leasebacks, 1967 (Box-folder 14/1)
      - Longview Fibre Company Pension Plan, 1959-1967 (Box-folder 14/2)